Mohamed Mahmoud Kosba

Cairo, Egypt | Flutter Developer | Website to check my apps



mohamed.kosba96@gmail.com

+20 1010152378 | WhatsApp

in linkedin.com/in/kosbaship

A https://kosbaship.github.io/site/

Summary

I have almost a year of experience in Flutter after two years of Android development, and SOLID is not just a word for me in Dart, I am more than familiar with Dio, RxDart, Getlt, Bloc/Cubit, Repository and Dependency Injection pattern and also up-to-date with the mobile landscape, architectures, trends, and emerging technologies.

Projects:

Cloth-Shop (Cubit – Firebase)

This app is an online Course-Shop.

Check The App Click Here

Courses-Shop (Cubit – Dio)

This app is an online Course-Shop.

Check The App Click Here

Chatting (Firebase - ListView - Animations)

This app lets you join a general chat room.

Check The App Click Here

Weather (API – Location - Permissions)

This app displays the current location and get any specific country location.

Check The App Click Here

Experience



Flutter Developer Intern

Softagi

Sep 2020 - Jan 2021 (5 months)



Android Developer

It Sharks

Oct 2018 - Mar 2019 (6 months)



Android Developer Instructor

Microsoft Student Partners

Aug 2017 - Apr 2018 (9 months)

Education



University of the People

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2021



Udacity

Advanced Android Developer 2015 - 2018

Military State: Exempted